<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Assassin</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="healthTut">
        This is your health. To heal, tap your health.
    </string>
    <string name="armorTut">
        This is your armor. To equip armor, tap your armor.
    </string>
    <string name="attackTut">
        This is your weapon damage. To equip a weapon, tap your weapon damage.
        Next to your weapon damage there is an attack counter.
    </string>
    <string name="attackButtonTut">
        Tap this button when you attack and your attack counter will go down.
    </string>
    <string name="takeDamageButTut">
        Use the number scroller to indicate how much damage you want to take, then tap
        "Take Damage". If you want damage to ignore your armor, toggle the "direct" switch.
    </string>
    <string name="undoTut">
        This is an undo button. It will undo the last damage calculation.
    </string>
   <string name="healpTut">
       Tap here if you want to run through help again.
   </string>

    <string name="aboutString">
        Assassination App for Android \n
        Version 1.0.0 \n\n

        Assassination and the Assassination\n
        logos are trademarks of Assassination Inc.\n
        All rights reserved.\n\n

        For any and all inquiries please email us \n
        at sdstrong222@gmail.com
    </string>

    <string-array name="HowToTitleStrings">
        <item>Set Up</item>
        <item>Turns</item>
        <item>Weapons and Armor</item>
        <item>Ability (Red) Cards</item>
        <item>Effect (Green) Cards</item>
        <item>Enchantment (Purple) Cards</item>
        <item>The Field</item>
        <item>Deaths</item>
        <item>How to Win</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="HowToDescripStrings">
        <item>
            Shuffle role cards and distribute one to each player. You can never show your role card to
            another player. Each player begins with 1000 Health Points (HP) \n\n

            For 4 Players: Assassin, Queen, King, and Jack \n
            For 5 Players: 2 Assassins. Queen, King, and Jack \n
            For 6 Players: 3 Assassins. Queen, King, and Jack \n\n

            Every Player begins with 5 cards and no one can attack with their weapon on their first turn
        </item>
        <item>
            Draw one card at the start of each turn. A player can choose to play an ability card, replace
            any weapons and armors, donate cards to any other player, or declare an attack. Attacking is done
            last in a turn. No one can attack on their first turn. At the end of a player’s turn, they can be
            holding no more than 7 cards. Any extra cards must be donated or discarded.
        </item>
        <item>
            Only one weapon and one armor may be equipped at a time. A player’s weapon and armor can be
            replaced at the end of any player’s turn, after they attack, or on their own turn. If a
            weapon or armor is already equipped but the player wants to equip a new one, the player may
            discard the weapon or armor and play another one from their hand. A weapon can only be used
            to attack 3 times. If the attack is stopped, it does not count as an attack for the weapon.
            Tier 1, 2, and 3 weapons deal 100, 200, and 300 damage respectively. Armor takes damage from
            a weapon instead of it being taken from a player’s HP. Tier 1, 2, and 3 armors have 100, 200,
            and 300 health. An armor’s health is different from a player’s HP. When an armor loses all of
            its health, the armor is destroyed and the remaining damage is dealt to the player’s HP. For
            example, if a tier 3 armor gets hit by a tier 1 weapon, then that armor takes the 100 damage
            and now has 200 health left to protect the player. If a tier 3 weapon hits a tier 1 armor,
            the armor is destroyed and the player takes 200 damage to their HP. If a weapon attacks a
            player with equal tiers, then the armor is destroyed and no damage is taken.
        </item>
        <item>
            Ability cards can only be played on the player’s turn. A player can only play one ability
            card per turn unless specified otherwise.
        </item>
        <item>
            Effect cards can be played on any turn, usually when a person is being attacked or targeted.
        </item>
        <item>
            Purple cards are enchantments on weapons and armors. They can only be played on the
            player’s turn. Multiple can be played in one turn and multiple can be applied to the
            same weapon or armor. The enchantment card is discarded when the weapon or armor is
            destroyed. If a card’s possession changes, the enchantments move with it.
        </item>
        <item>
            The “field” encompasses all the cards on the table. There is a draw pile, a discard pile,
            and each player’s own section of the field. In a player’s section, they should have their
            role card face down and their HP visible if asked for. If a card is played that targets a
            player, it is placed on their side of the field. For example, if Player A plays Bound on
            Player B, it is kept on Player B’s field until the effect is over.
        </item>
        <item>
            When a player dies, they discard their hand and cannot disclose any information on
            their roles or any other players’. The dead player must look at every person’s role and
            determine if the game is over or if they must continue playing. The player who does the
            killing gains 200 HP (cannot go above 1000 HP) and draws 2 cards. If multiple players’
            cards are responsible for the death, then no players collect the reward.
        </item>
        <item>
            Assassin: The assassins win by killing the King, Queen, and Jack.\n\n
            King: The King wins by surviving with the Queen. If the Queen dies, the King cannot win,
            but may still be the last player to survive.\n\n
            Queen: The Queen wins by surviving with the King or the Jack (only if the King is dead).\n\n
            Jack: The Jack wins by surviving with the Queen, but must kill the King. If the Queen dies,
            the Jack cannot win, but may be the last player to survive.\n\n
            The game ends when there is only one person alive, only Assassins alive, or when the Queen
            survives with the King or Jack.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="setuparray">
        <item>Set Up</item>
    <item>
        Shuffle role cards and distribute one to each player. You can never show your role card to
        another player. Each player begins with 1000 Health Points (HP) \n\n

        For 4 Players: Assassin, Queen, King, and Jack \n
        For 5 Players: 2 Assassins. Queen, King, and Jack \n
        For 6 Players: 3 Assassins. Queen, King, and Jack \n\n

        Every Player begins with 5 cards and no one can attack with their weapon on their first turn
    </item>
    <item>
        Draw one card at the start of each turn. A player can choose to play an ability card, replace
        any weapons and armors, donate cards to any other player, or declare an attack. Attacking is done
        last in a turn. No one can attack on their first turn. At the end of a player’s turn, they can be
        holding no more than 7 cards. Any extra cards must be donated or discarded.
    </item>
        <item>
        Only one weapon and one armor may be equipped at a time. A player’s weapon and armor can be
        replaced at the end of any player’s turn, after they attack, or on their own turn. If a
        weapon or armor is already equipped but the player wants to equip a new one, the player may
        discard the weapon or armor and play another one from their hand. A weapon can only be used
        to attack 3 times. If the attack is stopped, it does not count as an attack for the weapon.
        Tier 1, 2, and 3 weapons deal 100, 200, and 300 damage respectively. Armor takes damage from
        a weapon instead of it being taken from a player’s HP. Tier 1, 2, and 3 armors have 100, 200,
        and 300 health. An armor’s health is different from a player’s HP. When an armor loses all of
        its health, the armor is destroyed and the remaining damage is dealt to the player’s HP. For
        example, if a tier 3 armor gets hit by a tier 1 weapon, then that armor takes the 100 damage
        and now has 200 health left to protect the player. If a tier 3 weapon hits a tier 1 armor,
        the armor is destroyed and the player takes 200 damage to their HP. If a weapon attacks a
        player with equal tiers, then the armor is destroyed and no damage is taken.
    </item>
        <item>Ability (Red) Cards</item>
        <item>
            Ability cards can only be played on the player’s turn. A player can only play one ability
            card per turn unless specified otherwise.
        </item>
        <item>Effect (Green) Cards </item>
        <item>
            Effect cards can be played on any turn, usually when a person is being attacked or targeted.
        </item>
        <item>Enchantment (Purple) Cards</item>
        <item>
            Purple cards are enchantments on weapons and armors. They can only be played on the
            player’s turn. Multiple can be played in one turn and multiple can be applied to the
            same weapon or armor. The enchantment card is discarded when the weapon or armor is
            destroyed. If a card’s possession changes, the enchantments move with it.
        </item>
        <item>The "Field"</item>
        <item>
            The “field” encompasses all the cards on the table. There is a draw pile, a discard pile,
            and each player’s own section of the field. In a player’s section, they should have their
            role card face down and their HP visible if asked for. If a card is played that targets a
            player, it is placed on their side of the field. For example, if Player A plays Bound on
            Player B, it is kept on Player B’s field until the effect is over.
        </item>
        <item>Deaths</item>
        <item>
            When a player dies, they discard their hand and cannot disclose any information on
            their roles or any other players’. The dead player must look at every person’s role and
            determine if the game is over or if they must continue playing. The player who does the
            killing gains 200 HP (cannot go above 1000 HP) and draws 2 cards. If multiple players’
            cards are responsible for the death, then no players collect the reward.
        </item>
        <item>How to win</item>
        <item>
            Assassin: The assassins win by killing the King, Queen, and Jack.\n\n
            King: The King wins by surviving with the Queen. If the Queen dies, the King cannot win,
            but may still be the last player to survive.\n\n
            Queen: The Queen wins by surviving with the King or the Jack (only if the King is dead).\n\n
            Jack: The Jack wins by surviving with the Queen, but must kill the King. If the Queen dies,
            the Jack cannot win, but may be the last player to survive.\n\n
            The game ends when there is only one person alive, only Assassins alive, or when the Queen
            survives with the King or Jack.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
